Finding Aid for Claude Thomas Stoner Photographs and Papers 1870s-1977
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Duplicate Material
  - Duplicate copy negatives (Box 13)
Western & Atlantic -- RM18, also unclassified photos under Famous engines and trains
Western Union Telegraph Co. -- P31, P66
Wheeling & Lake Erie -- WLE1, also unclassified photos under this name
White, A.J.-- see Crescent & Southeastern
Wild Goose Railroad -- CX9
Wilson, Luther & Wilson -- LR216-217
Wisconsin Land & Lumber Co. -- see unclassified photos under this name; see also Blaney & Southern and Hermansville & Western
Wm. Crippen & Son -- LR165, LR192-193, LR223-224
Wm. T. Addis & Co. -- see Spring Harbor Railroad
Woodstock Lumber Co. -- RM5
Worcester Lumber Co. -- see Houghton, Chassell & Southwestern
Worden, J.H. -- LR226-228
Wright & Ketchum -- FPM12; see also its successor J.E. Potts Salt & Lumber Co.
Wyandotte Southern -- see unclassified photos under this name
Yellow Poplar Lumber Co. -- CX8
Yuill Bros. -- LR56
Addison, Mich. -- see unclassified negatives under Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Adrian, Mich. -- TW21, also unclassified photos and negatives under Railroad stations
Index to Subjects Other than Locomotives
Agricultural machinery -- GTR13, IR17, also unclassified photos under Illinois Central, and unclassified negatives under Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Alaska -- CX9
Alba, Mich. -- DC1
Albany, N.Y. -- NYC36
Albion, Mich. -- NYC7
Allen Junction, Ohio -- TW25
Alleyton, Mich. -- LR210-211
Alma, Mich. -- AA22
Alpena, Mich. -- LR112
Alvordton, Ohio -- TW23
Ann Arbor, Mich. --
AA21, AA76-78, AA98-99, AA131, AA149-152, AA156, AA160, AA181-182, AA208-211, AA218, AA221-222, AA234, AA258-262, AASR3-5
CO8, FT1-5, GM1-4, GTW25-27, MC19, MC53, MC56-57, MER1-7, NYC3, NYC12-15, NYC35
See also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad, Ann Arbor Street Railway, Michigan Central, New York Central, Railroad stations, Union Pacific, and University of Michigan, and unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad, Ann Arbor Street Railway, and New York Central
Annpere, Mich. -- PM3, PM6-7, X6, also unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Ashley, Mich. -- AA204, AA233, GTR21, GTR82
Aultsville, Ont. -- GTR89
Au Train, Mich. -- DSSA24
Bad Axe, Mich. -- GTR13
Bad River, Wis. DSSA17-18
Bannister, Mich. -- AA87-88, AA164, AA229-231
Barts Lick, Va. -- CX8
Battle Creek, Mich. -- GTR86, IR17, M7, M14
Bay City, Mich. -- GTW39, X2-3
Bay Point, Mich. -- AA85, AA97, AA201-202
Bay Springs, Mich. -- LR175
Bay View, Mich. -- see unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Bear Lake, Mich. -- LR23-25, LR75-76, LR218
Beaver Island, Mich. -- LR14-16, LR77, LR185, PM42, PM105
Bendon, Mich. -- PM34
Benton Harbor, Mich. -- see unclassified negatives under Railroad stations
Benzonia, Mich. -- FSE7-9
Bergland, Mich. -- LR39
Beulah, Mich. -- AA162, AA219, FSE4, FSE5a-5c, FSE6
Big Rapids, Mich. -- LR104, LR106, PM50
Birmingham, Mich. -- GTW5-6
Blanchard, Mich. -- LR255
Blissfield, Mich. -- TW27, TW28
Bond's Mills, Mich. -- GRI21
Boon, Mich. -- AA116, AA176
Boston, Mass. -- SR3
Boyne City, Mich. -- BC5
Boyne Falls, Mich. -- BC4, LR60, also unclassified negatives under Boyne City Railroad
Breckenridge, Mich. -- DLN17
Bridal Veil, Ore. LR136
Brighton, Mich. -- PM127-129
Brookings, Mich. -- CWM5
Brooklyn, Mich. -- LSMS29
Buttersville, Mich. -- MO2
Cadillac, Mich. --
GRI47, LR1-3, LR5, LR8, LR38, LR50-55, LR82, LR85-86, LR107, LR123, LR137-138, LR140, LR142-144, LR169-170, LR179, LR225
also unclassified photos under Cadillac, Mich., views
Camp Grayling, Mich. -- MNE45
Carferries --
AA4, AA43-44, AA46, AA49, AA58-62, AA106-107, AA118-122, AA124, AA159, AA163, AA179, AA206-207, AA220, AA225, AA237-243
CO3-4, CO14-15, DSSA21, DSSA38, GRI16, GTR70, GTR94, MMN1-4, P1-4
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad and unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad, Pere Marquette, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics
Carson City, Mich. -- GTR16
Cass River, Mich. -- PM116
Cedar Point, Ohio -- CPLE1-8
Cedar Springs, Mich. -- LR226-228
Central Lake, Mich. -- PM131
Charlevoix, Mich. -- PM36
Charlotte, Mich. -- MC55
Chase, Mich. -- LR19, LR36, LR141, LR178, LR180, LR182, PM97
Cheboygan, Mich. -- MC62, also unclassified photos under Detroit & Mackinac
Chelsea, Mich. --
MC26, MC58, NYC8-10, NYC19, NYC45, NYC47
Also unclassified photos under Michigan Central and Railroad stations, and unclassified negatives under Train wrecks
Chilson, Mich. -- AA71, AA145, IR6-7
Chippewa Lake, Mich. -- LR229-230
Clam River, Mich. -- LR148
Clare, Mich. -- AA129
Clarion, Mich. -- GRI8-9, GRI44
Clinton, Mich. -- LSMS24-25
Comber, Ont. -- MC59
Coopersville, Mich. -- GTR91-93
Copemish, Mich. -- AA155
Coral, Mich. -- PM17
Corrie, Pa. CX14
Corunna, Mich. -- AA235, OCT1
Cranesville, W. Va. -- CX1
Crawler tractors -- LR69-71, LR93, LR212, LR214-215, also unclassified negatives under National Railroad Museum
Cresceus, Ohio -- TW26
Crofton, Mich. -- LR125
Crossing guards -- AA30
Croton, Mich. -- see unclassified negatives under Croton Dam
Crystal City, Mich. -- see Beulah, Mich.
Crystal Lake, Mich. -- FSE4, FSE5a-5c
Dade City, Fla. -- LR89-90
Dams -- see unclassified negatives under Croton Dam
Deer Lake (Lake County), Mich. -- LR160
Dempsey, Mich. -- PM45, PM49
Detroit, Mich. -- DSR1-8, GTW83, also unclassified photos and albums under Detroit River Tunnel Co.
Detroit River, Mich. and Ont. -- see unclassified photos and albums under Detroit River Tunnel Co.
Detroit Zoo, Mich. -- see unclassified photos under Miscellaneous locomotives (line identified)
Deward, Mich. -- LR58
Dewey, Thomas E.-- see unclassified photos under New York Central
Dexter, Mich. -- MC1, MC29, NYC4, NYC24, NYC31, NYC42-43, also unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Dighton, Mich. -- LR95, MGR5
Drummond Island, Mich. -- LR161
Dryden, Mich. -- PON1
Dundee, Mich. -- AA130
Durand, Mich. --
AA161, GTR2, GTR7, GTR14, GTR17, GTR28, GTR62, GTR67, GTR75, GTW20-23, GTW38, GTW65
Also unclassified negatives under Grand Trunk Western and Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Eagle River, Wis. -- LR146
East Jordan, Mich. -- EJS1, EJS3-5, also unclassified negatives under East Jordan & Southern
East Tawas, Mich. -- DM8
Eastlake, Mich. -- ML1-2
Eaton Rapids, Mich. -- MC25
Edmore, Mich. -- LR109
Edwardsburg, Mich. -- GTR85
Elberta, Mich. -- AA96 (see also Frankfort, Mich. entries)
Elsie, Mich. -- AA137-139, AA227-228
Escanaba, Mich. -- CNW2
Falmouth, Mich. -- LR148
Fenton, Mich. -- SR5, SR9, SR11
Filer City, Mich. -- MGR1, MGR3, MGR7-9
Flint, Mich. -- GTR19
Forest Hill, Mich. -- AA212
Four Mile Lake, Mich. -- NYC40
Fowlerville, Mich. -- DLN3-6, DLN16
Frankfort, Mich. --
AA43-44, AA46-53, AA59-62, AA106-107, AA118-120, AA123-124, AA159, AA179, AA200, AA206-207, AA217, AA225, AA232, AA238-240, AA242-243, MMN1-2
Also unclassified photos and negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad and Frankfort, Mich., views
Fremont, Mich. -- CWM20, PM30
Gananoque, Ont. -- TI3
Gaylord, Mich. -- MC32
Gilchrist, Mich. -- Soo1
Glen Haven, Mich. -- LR91-92
Goshen, Ind. -- see unclassified negatives under Railroad stations
Grand Junction, Mich. -- PM44
Grand Ledge, Mich. -- DLN1, DLN19, PM40-41, also unclassified photos under Grand Ledge, Mich., views
Grand Rapids, Mich. -- GRR1-8, SR7-8
Grass Lake, Mich. -- DJC3, MC46-48, also unclassified negatives under Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Grayling, Mich. -- LR59, LR174, MC18, MC49, MC66-67
Grays River, Wash. -- CX10-11
Greenville, Mich. -- GTR72, GTW24
Grindstone City, Mich. -- PM95
Hancock, Mich. -- DSSA33
Hamburg, Mich. -- see unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad
Handicapped -- AA30
Hanover, Mich. -- LSMS12
Harbor Springs, Mich. --
GRI23, LR9-12, LR40-42, LR48-49. LR83, LR111, LR113, LR127-132, LR147, LR151, LR195-200, LR246
Also unclassified photos and negatives under Shay
Harbors AA43, AA49, AA59-62, AA106-107, AA118, AA120, AA124, AA206-207, AA217, AA242-243, LR219, also unclassified photos and negatives under Frankfort, Mich., views
Haring, Mich. -- GRI4, LR145
Hart, Mich. -- LR87-88
Hawk Junction, Ont. -- see unclassified negatives under Railroad stations
Hermansville, Mich. -- LR118-119
Hesperia, Mich. -- LR162
Honor, Mich. -- MNE34
Horse cars SR5, SR8-9, SR11, X7
Hotels -- AA123-124, AA217, also unclassified photos and negatives under Frankfort, Mich., views
Houghton, Mich. -- DSSA19
Howard City, Mich. -- DLN15
Howell, Mich. --
AA23-30, AA80-83, AA125-127, AA184, AA263, PM1-2, PM4, PM120
Also unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad, Pere Marquette, Railroad stations, and Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Hoxeyville, Mich. -- ML16, ML19
Hudson, Mich. -- LSMS36-38, NOR1-2, also unclassified negatives under Railroad stations
Hunting -- see unclassified photos under Frankfort, Mich., views, and unclassified negatives under Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Huron, Ohio -- WLE1
Huron River, Mich. --
AA131, AA149, AA208-210, AA221-222, AA258-262, GTW25-27, MC2
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad and unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad and New York Central
Ice bridges -- LR148
Imlay City, Mich. -- GTW14
Interurbans -- see Street railroads
Iron Bridge, Mich. -- DSSA15
Jackson, Mich. -- GTW7-9, GTW60-61, GTW63-64, M1-2, NYC27-29
Jennings, Mich. -- LR139, LR194, LR207-208, LR232, also unclassified photos and negatives under Jennings, Mich., views
Jerome, Mich. -- LSMS39
Kalamazoo, Mich. -- M11, MC7a, also unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Kalkaska, Mich. -- PM99
Keno (Newaygo County), Mich. -- LR202
Kibbie, Mich. -- MC52
Lacoochee, Fla. LR78-81, also unclassified photos and negatives under Cummer Sons Cypress Co.
Lake City, Mich. -- CLC9, LR149, LR238, also unclassified negatives under Railroad stations
Lake Lansing, Mich. -- X12
Lake Odessa, Mich. -- PM63, also unclassified photos under Detroit, Lansing & Northern
Lakeland, Mich. -- AA69-70, AA148, AA223
Lakeview, Mich. -- DLN13
L'Anse, Mich. -- DSSA1-3
Lansing, Mich. -- CO10, CO12-13, SR2, also unclassified photos under Lake Shore & Michigan Southern, and unclassified negatives under Street railroads
Lewiston, Mich. -- MC24, MC50-51
Lifesaving service -- see unclassified photos and negatives under Frankfort, Mich., views
Lincoln. N.H. -- LR46
Logging and logging railroads --
AA32, ABR6-7, ABR10, ABR12, CWM14-15, CWM18, CX1-2, CX4, CX6-8, CX10-11, CX15, FPM4, FPM12-13, FPM21, FPM24, FPM27, GRI31, LC1-9, LR1-258
MGR3, ML1-2, ML5, ML9-10, ML18, ML21-23, MNE2, MNE16, MNE38, MO1-9, NN1, PM42, PM45-46, PM48, PM105, Soo6
also unclassified photos under Cadillac, Mich., views, Cummer Sons Cypress Co., Frankfort, Mich., views, Jennings, Mich., views, Logging and logging railroads, Shay, and Sykes, W.L., and unclassified negatives under Cummer Sons Cypress Co., Hobart & Manistee, Logging and logging railroads, Shay, and Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Ludington, Mich. -- CO3-4, CO14-15, LN1-5, also unclassified negatives under Pere Marquette
Lupton, Mich. -- DM7
Luther, Mich. -- LR216-217
Lyons, Ohio -- TW22
Mable, Mich. -- PM100, PM103, PM110-113
McDermott, Ohio -- CX5
McKinley, Mich. -- LR64-66
Mackinaw City, Mich. -- GRI16
Mammoth Cave, Ky. -- see unclassified negatives under Mammoth Cave Railroad
Mancelona, Mich. -- LR47, LR74, LR121
Manchester, Mich. -- LSMS26
Manistee, Mich. -- LR28, LR120, LR203-205, MGR6, MNE8-11, NMT1-5, SR1, also unclassified negatives under Flint & Pere Marquette
Manistee River, Mich. -- GRI30, LR154, PM10, PM83
Manistique, Mich. -- AA121-122, AA220, also unclassified photos and negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad
Marion, Mich. -- AA36-40, AA186, also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad
Marquette, Mich. -- DSSA31, DSSA36-37
Marshall, Mich. -- NYC16-17, X9-10, also unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Mason, Mich. -- MC64
Mears, Mich. -- PM81
Merrill, Mich. -- DLN12
Merritt, Mich. -- LR155
Mesick, Mich. -- AA33-35
Mikado, Mich. -- DM1
Milan, Mich. -- AA94
Milford, Mich. -- see unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Mill Creek, Mich. -- NYC31
Millersville, Mich. -- AA189-197, also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad
Missaukee City, Mich. -- LR35
Missaukee Junction, Mich. -- GRI2, GRI4
Montpelier, Ohio -- X13
Moorestown, Mich. -- LR150
Morenci, Mich. -- TW29
Morley, Mich. -- LR163
Motor Cars --
AA24-27, AA71, AA127, AA214, AA223, AA227-228, GTW53, MK1-2, MK5, NYC26, NYC34
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad and unclassified negatives under McKeen Motor Car Co.
Mount Dora, Fla.-- see unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Mount Pleasant, Mich. -- FPM23
Mount Washington, N.H. -- MW1-10, also unclassified photos under Mount Washington Cog Railway
Muskegon, Mich. -- GRI15
Muskegon River, Mich. -- LR155
Nahma Junction, Mich. -- NN1
Nashville, Tenn. -- NC1
Nessen City, Mich. -- MNE13
New Era, Mich. -- LR168
North Branch, Mich. -- GTR31
North Carolina -- CX2
North Lansing, Mich. -- MC9
North Manitou Island, Mich. -- LR239
Northport, Mich. -- MMN3
Northville, Mich. -- see unclassified negatives under Train wrecks
Onaway, Mich. -- LR37
Onekama, Mich. -- MNE44
Ontonagon, Mich. -- LR244
Ontonagon River, Mich. -- DSSA20
Ore docks -- DSSA31, DSSA36
Orleans, Mich. -- PM85
Oshawa, Ont. -- OR1
Otter Lake, Mich. -- MC27-28
Owosso, Mich. -- AA136, AA144, AA174, M8, OCT1
Palms (Sanilac County), Mich. -- FPM25
Park Lake, Mich. -- AA203
Parma, Mich. -- M19-21, MC44-45
Peacock, Mich. -- PM90
Pellston, Mich. -- LR94
Perch River, Mich. -- DSSA16
Perrinton, Mich. -- GTW74
Peterboro, N.H. see unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Petoskey, Mich. -- GRI36-40, also unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Petrolia, Ont. -- CNR1-2
Pierport, Mich. -- LR219
Pinchtown, Mich. -- LR242
Pomona, Mich. -- AA244-257
Pompeii, Mich. -- see unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Port Huron, Mich. -- FPM11, GTW1, GTW3, SCT1-11
Railroad accidents --
AA33-35, AA40-42, AA63-68, AA87-88, AA94, AA98-99, AA102, AA125-127, AA139, AA150-151, AA181-182, AA186-197, AA211, AA244-257, BC2-3, CNW6, CX11, DLN3-6, DLN16, DSSA1-3, DSSA36, FPM22
GRI1, GRI8-9, GRI21-22, GRI32-34, GRI36-45, GRI48, GTR8-11, GTR20, GTR72-74, GTR82, GTW83, LR15-16, LR65, LR168, LSMS23, M21, MC7b, MC26-27, MC47-48, MC50-52, MC66-67, MER1-7, MGR1-2, MGR7-8, MNE8-11, NYC13-15, PM7, PM29, PM37-39, PM59-62, PM86, PM97-100, PM103, PM107-113, PM121-124, PM127-129, SR6, STH1
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad, Michigan Central, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics, and unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad, Train wrecks, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics
Railroad bridges --
AA131, AA149-151, AA164, AA181-182, AA205, AA208-210, AA218, AA221-222, AA258-262, ABR6-7, BC7, CO5, CO8, CX9
DLN1, DLN19, DM11, DSSA14-18, DSSA20, DSSA24, DSSA28, GRI30, GTW25-27, GTW78, LC5, LC9, LR67, LR104, LR154, LR164, LR184, LR188, LR218, LR221-222, LR232, LR249, LSMS26, LSMS39
MC2, MC4-5, MC16-17, MC20, MC39, ML5, ML10, ML14, NYC31, PM10, PM30, PM36, PM41, PM83, PM116, TW21
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad, Michigan Central, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics, unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad, High bridge, Lake Shore & Michigan Southern, New York Central, Tweetsie Railroad, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics, and albums under Michigan Central
Railroad cars and equipment --
AA31-32, AA45, AA110, AA116, AA132, AA146-147, AA150-151, AA158, AA181-182, AA186, AA204-205, AA218, AA221, AA244-257, BC7
CLC1-3, CLC13, CO13, CWM8, CWM11-12, CWM14-15, DLN17, DSSA15, DSSA23, DSSA25-26, DSSA29, EJS6
FPM4, FPM8, FPM11, FPM17, FSE6, GRI9, GRI28, GRI34, GRI36-43, GRI48, GTR13, GTR18, GTR32-34, GTR81, GTR88, GTW22, GTW71, IR4, JTKW1
LC1-5, LC7, LN1-2, LN5, LR9, LR11-12, LR16-17, LR19, LR28, LR40-41, LR48, LR56-57, LR59-61, LR87-88, LR132, LR144, LR159, LR171, LR204-205, LR241, LR243, LSI1
MC11, MC14-16, MC21, MC32-33, MC39, MGR6, ML23, MLS3, MNE12, MNE15, MNE34, MNE47, MO7, NW6, NYC3, NYC15
PM30, PM47, PM80, PM98, PM108-109, PM115, PM119, PM122, PM124, PM127, PM132, RM14-15, SCT8, TAJ3, TW5-25, TW30-31, TW34-38
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad, Atchison, Topeka & Santa Fe, Baltimore & Ohio, Canadian National, Chesapeake & Ohio, Chicago & North Western, Chicago, Burlington & Quincy, Cummer Sons Cypress Co., Detroit & Lima Northern, Illinois Central, Michigan Central, New York Central, Pennsylvania Railroad, Pere Marquette, Soo Line, Wabash, Wheeling & Lake Erie, Miscellaneous freight cars, and Miscellaneous rail cars, unclassified negatives under Escanaba & Lake Superior, New York Central, Miscellaneous locomotives, and Miscellaneous rail cars, and albums under Michigan Central
Railroad construction -- CWM11-12, see also unclassified photos under Detroit & Mackinac, Detroit River Tunnel Co., and Frankfort, Mich., views, and albums under Detroit River Tunnel Co. and Michigan Central
Railroad stations --
AA22-23, AA25-29, AA70, AA76-80, AA115-117, AA129-130, AA135-138, AA145, AA175-176, AA203-204, AA212-213, AA219, AA227-231, AA233-235, AA263
BC4-5, CLC9, CPLE5-6, CWM20, DJC3, DLN19, DM1, EJS1, EJS5, FPM11, FSE4, FSE7-8
GRI4, GRI23, GRI25, GRI46, GTR14, GTR16-17, GTR19, GTR31, GTR62, GTR67, GTR71, GTR75, GTR85, GTR89, GTW5-6, GTW38, GTW65, GTW74
LR138, LSMS12, LSMS22, LSMS24-25, LSMS37-38
M19, MC1, MC9-10, MC13, MC19, MC24-25, MC28-29, MC41, MC44-46, MC49, MC55-56, MC58-59, MC61-65, MNE13-14, MNE34-37, MNE44, MNE46
NC1, NYC12-13, NYC24, NYC27-29, NYC34, NYC38, NYC42-43
PM1, PM17, PM27-28, PM34, PM40, PM44, PM51, PM56, PM63, PM81-82, PM85, PM89-90, PM95, PM102, PM104, PM114, PM117, PM120, PM130-131, PON1
Soo1, TI3, TW22-23, TW26-27, TW33
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad, Railroad stations, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics, and unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad, Boyne City Railroad, East Broad Top, Grand Trunk Western, Pere Marquette, Railroad stations, and Tweetsie Railroad
Railroad tunnels -- DRT1-6, SCT1-11, also unclassified photos and albums under Detroit River Tunnel Co.
Railroad workers --
AA1, AA3, AA5, AA30, AA65, AA68, AA83, AA85-86, AA93-95, AA104-105, AA109-112, AA116, AA132-134, AA136, AA153-156, AA198-200, AA236, AA255-257, AASR1-2, AAY3, ABR3, ABR8-9, ABR11
BC4-5, BC7-10, BMR1, CC1, CJ1, CWM1-5, CWM9-13, CWM19, CWM21-24, CX1-7, CX10, CX15
DJC1-2, DLN7, DLN9-11, DLN13-15, DLN18, DM3-5, DM7, DM9, DSSA5-9, DSSA33-35, DSSA37, DTSL3, EJS1, ESE1, FPM6-9, FPM13, FPM15-16, FPM20, FPM25, FPM27, FSE3
GRI6, GRI10-13, GRI20, GRI24, GRI27-28, GRI29, GRI31-32, GRI35, GTR2-6, GTR15, GTR17, GTR21-26, GTR28, GTR30, GTR63-66, GTR68-69, GTR75-76, GTR79-80, GTR86, GTR90, GTR95, GTW30, GTW55
IR15-16, LC1-3, LC6-9, LR1-4, LR6, LR13-17, LR22-25, LR28, LR36-42, LR44-45, LR50-52, LR56-57, LR59-61, LR72, LR76-77, LR85-87, LR93-94, LR102-105, LR108-110, LR112, LR118-121
LR125-128, LR132, LR134-135, LR139-140, LR146, LR149, LR151, LR156-163, LR167-169, LR174-176, LR178, LR182-183, LR185-187, LR198-201, LR203-204, LR206-210, LR212-217
LR222, LR225-231, LR233-238, LR240-241, LR243, LR245, LR251-258, LSI3, LSI5, LSMS2-8, LSMS10-11, LSMS19, LSMS21, LSMS27, LSMS35
Man1, MC3, MC6-7a, MC13-14, MC18, MC22, MC34-37, MC39-42, MC54, MC59-60, MGR3-6, ML3-4, ML6, ML8, ML11-12-13, ML15-17, ML19-20, ML22-24, MNE5, MNE20-31, MNE40, MNE47, MNE49
MO1, MO3-6, MO8-9, MR2, MRY2, MSE1, NMT1, NYC36, OCT1
PM14-16, PM19, PM24, PM33, PM35, PM42-43, PM46, PM49-50, PM52, PM57, PM84, PM86, PM88, PM96, PM105-106, PM108-109, PM115
SH1, Soo2, Soo6, STH3, TAJ1-2, TTC1, TW2-3, TW8-9, TW12, TW14-15, TW17, TW19, TW23, Van1, W4, W10, WLE1
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad, Ann Arbor Street Railway, Central Pacific, Columbus, Chicago & Indiana Central, Detroit & Mackinac, Detroit, Grand Rapids & Western, Detroit River Tunnel Co., Detroit, Toledo & Ironton, Duluth, South Shore & Atlantic, Lake Shore & Michigan Southern, Logging and logging railroads, Miscellaneous locomotives (line unidentified), Miscellaneous rail cars, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics, unclassified negatives under Chicago & West Michigan, Hobart & Manistee, Logging and logging railroads, Street railroads, Welding rail joints, Miscellaneous locomotives, and Miscellaneous various railroad topics, and albums under Detroit River Tunnel Co. and Michigan Central
Railroad yards and shops --
AA47-48, AA50-53, AA106, CNW2, CP1, DM5, DSSA19, FPM25, GTR7, GTR86, GTW35, GTW83, LR106, LR240, LR256
MC11, MC21, MC49, MC56, MNE37, NC1, PM19, PM22, TW30, TW32, TW34-35, TW41
Also unclassified photos under Detroit River Tunnel Co., Flint & Pere Marquette, and Miscellaneous railroad topics, unclassified negatives under Miscellaneous various railroad topics, and albums under Detroit River Tunnel Co.
Rainestown, Pa. -- see unclassified photos under Logging and logging railroads
Rapid City, Mich. -- PM114
Red Bluff, Calif. -- CX15
Reed City, Mich. -- GRI46, PM102, PM117
Ricker, Mich. -- CWM11-13
Rifle River, Mich. -- DM11
Rogers City, Mich. -- LR69-70
Roscommon, Mich. -- see unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Rose City, Mich. -- DM5
Roseburg, Ore. -- CP1
Rushton, Mich. -- GTR60, GTW53
St. Helen, Mich. -- LR176-177
St. Ignace, Mich. -- DSSA38
St. Louis, Mich. -- PM121-122, PM130
Salem, Mich. -- PM29, PM59-62
Saline, Mich. -- NYC38
San Francisco, Calif. -- X7
Sandusky, Ohio -- see unclassified negatives under Lake Shore & Michigan Southern
Sanger, Calif. -- LR188
Saranac, Mich. -- GTR71
Sault Ste. Marie, Mich. -- DSSA14, DSSA28, LR93, also unclassified negatives under Duluth, South Shore & Atlantic
Sharon, Mich. -- see unclassified negatives under Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Sheffield, Pa. -- CX12
Shelby, Mich. -- PM82, PM108-109, PM119
Shelldrake, Mich. -- LR214-215
Shepherd, Mich. -- AA175
Sherbrooke, Que. -- GTR73-74
Sherman, Mich. -- AA187, also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Railroad
Ships --
AA207, AA217, LSMS30
Also unclassified photos under Frankfort, Mich., views, and Ships, unclassified negatives under Flint & Pere Marquette, Frankfort, Mich., views, and Shay, and albums under Detroit River Tunnel Co.
Shipwrecks -- AA44, AA121-122, AA179, AA225, AA232, AA239, also unclassified photos and negatives under Ann Arbor Railroad
Sigma, Mich. -- MNE46, PM24
Six Lakes, Mich. -- LR108
Smithville (Kalkaska County), Mich. -- LR154, LR184
Soldiers -- AAY2
South Haven, Mich. -- MC40
South Lyon, Mich. -- GTR59, PM27-28
Spencer, Mich. -- LR231, LR235, PM48
Spring Arbor, Mich. -- MC61, also unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Spring Lake, Mich. -- LR4
Standish, Mich. -- MC65
Stearns, Mich. -- PM86
Stoner, Claude T. -- X15, also unclassified photos under Miscellaneous non-railroad topics
Stratford, Mich. -- CWM18, LR183, LR186, LR258, PM56, also unclassified photos and negatives under Logging and logging railroads
Street railroads --
AASR1-5, AAY1-5, DJC1-3, DRT6, DSR1-8, GRR1-8, Int1, M1-21, MER1-7, NMT1-5, OCT1, SR1-11, TTC1, TW1-41, X7
Also unclassified photos under Ann Arbor Street Railway and Detroit & River St. Clair Railway, and unclassified negatives under Ann Arbor Street Railway, Lake Shore & Michigan Southern, Street railroads, and Miscellaneous rail cars
Sturgeon Bay, Mich. -- LR13, LR17
Suttons Bay, Mich. -- GRI17, also unclassified photos under Grand Rapids & Indiana
Svensen, Ore. -- CX6-7
Sylvania, Ohio -- TW30
Tawas City, Mich. -- LR114
Tecumseh, Mich. -- LSMS22-23
Thompsonville, Mich. -- AA213-214, PM89, PM104, also unclassified negatives under Railroad stations
Tionesta Creek, Pa. -- CX3
Tittabawassee River, Mich. -- FPM12
Toledo, Ohio -- AA79, TTC1
Topinabee, Mich. -- MC63
Tramways -- LR27, LR180
Traverse City, Mich. -- GRI25, LR96-100, MNE14, MNE35-37, PM19, PM22, also unclassified photos under Logging and logging railroads
Trenary, Mich. -- see unclassified photos under Railroad stations
Trout Creek, Mich. -- LR67-68
Trowbridge (Cheboygan County), Mich. -- LR61
Tustin, Mich. -- GRI33-34, GRI48
Urania, Mich. -- AA117, AA224
Vanderbilt, Mich. -- LR56
Vassar, Mich. -- PM116